Finding Aid for the Kelly Miller Smith Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- ORGANIZATIONS
  - World Council of Churches, Commission on Faith and Order, Conferences, Bangalore, India, August 15 - 20, 1978 (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - World Council of Churches, Commission on Faith and Order, Conferences, Lima, Peru, November 1981, Brochures (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - Mailing List (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - Notes (Box 138, Folder 6)
  - Papers (Box 138)
  - Address to the Plenary Commission on Faith and Order (Box 138, Folder 7)
  - Allpa Rayku (Box 138, Folder 8)
  - Baptism (Box 138, Folder 9)
  - "Capet Y La Inglesia Peruna" (Box 138, Folder 10)
  - Church Unity and the Renewal of the Human Community (Box 138, Folder 11)
  - The Community of Women and Men in the Church: Towards the Assembly and Beyond (Box 138, Folder 12)
  - The Contribution of the Community Study to the Assembly Preparation Programme (Box 138, Folder 13)
  - Corrections of Bem for Lima (Box 138, Folder 14)
  - Corrections to Ministry Document (Box 138, Folder 15)
  - Corrections to Preface (Box 138, Folder 16)
  - Ecumenical Importance of the Nicene-Constantinopolitan Creed (Box 138, Folder 17)
  - El Exito, ¿Cuanto Nos Cuesta? (Box 138, Folder 18)
  - Eucharist (Box 138, Folder 19)
  - Eucharistic Celebrations at Ecumenical Gatherings (Box 138, Folder 20)
  - The Faith and Order Commission as a Witnessing Event (Box 138, Folder 21)
  - Identity and Relationships in the New Community (Box 138, Folder 22)
  - Introduction into the Study Towards the Common Expression of the Apostolic Faith Today (Box 138, Folder 23)
  - The Issue of Scripture in the Community Study (Box 138, Folder 24)
  - Kamaq Maki (Box 138, Folder 25)
  - La Reception (Box 138, Folder 26)
  - Life in Unity (Box 138, Folder 27)
  - Listening to Some Contemporary Statements of Faith from Latin America (Box 138, Folder 28)
  - One Baptism, One Eucharist and a Mutually Recognized Ministry (Box 138, Folder 29)
  - Recommendations from the CWMC Group to the Bem Group (Box 138, Folder 30)
  - Report from the Colombo Consultation of the United and Uniting Churches (Box 138, Folder 31)
  - Report of the Group on Church Unity Developments (Box 138, Folder 32)
  - Report of the Secretariat (Box 138, Folder 33)
  - The Roman Catholic Church and the United Churches (Box 138, Folder 34)
  - Some Contemporary Witnesses of Faith from Latin America (Box 138, Folder 35)
  - Towards the Common Expression of the Apostolic Faith Church Today (Box 138, Folder 36)
  - Towards Unity in Tension (Box 138, Folder 37)
  - United and Uniting Churches (Box 138, Folder 38)
  - Unity Between Hope and History (Box 138, Folder 39)
  - The Unity of the Church and the Renewal of Human Community (Box 138, Folder 40)
  - The Unity of the Church and the Renewal of Human Community: A Prospectus (Box 138, Folder 41)
  - World Council of Churches, Commission on Faith and Order, Conferences, University of Ghana, Legon, July 22 - August 5, 1974, Address List (Box 138, Folder 42)
  - General Information (Box 138, Folder 43)
  - Groups for Account of Hope Discussion (Box 138, Folder 44)
  - Hymns for Use in Worship Services (Box 138, Folder 45)
  - Notes Papers (Box 138, Folder 46)
  - Bible Study - Dr. Ellen Flesseman - Van Leer, The God From Afar (Box 138, Folder 47)
  - The Consensus of Baptism (Box 138, Folder 48)
  - Giving Account of the Hope that in in Us (Box 138, Folder 49)
  - Mankind (Box 138, Folder 50)
  - Rendre Compte de 'esperance qui est en nous (Box 138, Folder 51)
  - Report of the Committee on "Unity of the Church - Unity of Mankind" (Box 138, Folder 52)
  - Report of the Secretariat to the Commission (Box 138, Folder 53)
  - T.E.F. - Faith and Order Relationship (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - The Unity of the Church - The Goal and the Way (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - The Unity of the Church and the Unity of Mankind (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - Unity of the Church - Unity of Mankind (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - Programs (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - World Council of Churches, Commission on Faith and Order, Minutes, August 6 - 14, 1973 - July 18, 1977 (Box 139, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda (30) January 9, 1975 - March 1983, undated (Box 139, Folder 7)
  - Newsletter, August 1981 - February 1982, undated (Box 139, Folder 8)
  - Papers (Box 139)
  - Baptism, February 1981 (Box 139, Folder 9)
  - Baptism and Eucharist in Ecumenical Perspective, February 1974 (Box 139, Folder 10)
  - Concepts of Unity and Models of Union, October 1972 (Box 139, Folder 11)
  - Eucharist, March 1981 (Box 139, Folder 12)
  - The Ecumenical Movement and Church Law, May 1974 (Box 139, Folder 13)
  - Final Text of the Draft By-Laws for the Faith and Order Commission, April 1974 (Box 139, Folder 14)
  - Giving Account of the Hope that is Within Us, April 1973 (Box 139, Folder 15)
  - How the Church Teaches Authoritatively Today: An Ecumenical Inquiry, July 1974 (Box 139, Folder 16)
  - How the Unity of the Church Can be Achieved, undated (Box 139, Folder 17)
  - Jesus Christ Frees and Unites. 1975 (Box 139, Folder 18)
  - Ministry, July 1980 (Box 139, Folder 19)
  - Ministry, March 1981 (Box 139, Folder 20)
  - Mutual Recognition of Baptism in Interchurch Agreements, 1978 (Box 139, Folder 21)
  - The Ordained Ministry in Ecumenical Perspective, January 1974 (Box 139, Folder 22)
  - The Potential Contribution of "Baptism, Eucharist, Ministry" to the Wider Project "Towards the Common Expression of the Apostolic Faith Today," November 1981 (Box 139, Folder 23)
  - Reflections on the Methods of Faith and Order Study, January 1974 (Box 139, Folder 24)
  - Report of the Secretariat, November 1981 (Box 139, Folder 25)
  - Report of the Second Forum on Bilateral Conversations, 1979 (Box 139, Folder 26)
  - Staff Report of the Secretariat on Faith and Order, June 1974 (Box 139, Folder 27)
  - Unity Between Hope and History, December 1981 (Box 139, Folder 28)
  - The Unity of the Church - Next Steps, January 1974 (Box 139, Folder 29)
  - The Unity of the Church - The Unity of Humankind, January 1981 (Box 139, Folder 30)
  - The Unity of the Church - Unity of Mankind, July 1974 (Box 139, Folder 31)
  - Press Release, January 22, 1981 (Box 139, Folder 32)
  - Programme to Combat Racism (Box 139, Folder 33)
  - Yale Divinity School (Box 139, Folder 34)
  - YMCA Fund raising Committee (Box 139, Folder 35)
- EVENTS
  - ASA Philip Randolph, In Memoriam, June 3, 1979 (Box 139, Folder 36)
  - Association of Black Psychologists, Sept, 25, 1981 (Box 139, Folder 37)
  - Black and White Conference, 1972 (Box 139, Folder 38)
  - Black on Black Crime Conference, May 30 - 31, 1980 (Box 139, Folder 39)
  - Black Religion Writers' Workshop, July 13 - 17, 1981 (Box 139, Folder 40)
  - Black Studies in the 1980s: Beyond Disciplines, July 29 - 31, 1982 (Box 139, Folder 41)
  - Black Women in Ministry Conference, October 27 - 29, 1976 (Box 139, Folder 42)
  - Career Planning and Placement, Fisk University, October 13 - 14, 1980 (Box 139, Folder 43)
  - Case-Study Institute Sixth Summer Workshop, 1977 (Box 139, Folder 44)
  - Celebrate a Dream, 20 Years, The Ride to Freedom, July 1981 (Box 139, Folder 45)
  - The Church: What I Believe, 1980 (Box 139, Folder 46)
  - Commemoration Sermon, Harvard University Memorial Church, November 11, 1982 (Box 139, Folder 47)
  - Conference on Black Church Studies, April 10 - 11, 1975 (Box 139, Folder 48)
  - Confronting the Tensions in Black Religion, November 11 - 12, 1976 (Box 139, Folder 49)
  - Coronation, October 28, 1961 (Box 139, Folder 50)
  - Deinstitutionalization.. .Challenge and Change, September 29, 1978 (Box 139, Folder 51)
  - Exhibition of Photographs by Anthony Taylor, August 1981 (Box 139, Folder 52)
  - Faculty Recital, Blair School of Music, April 14, 1981 (Box 139, Folder 53)
  - Faith Expressed Through Action, April 13, 1980 (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - Family Crisis, The Role of the Community, November 7 - 8, undated (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - Fisk Inaugurates Dr. Leonard President, October 3, 1977 (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - Global and Transcultural Education, July - August 1979 (Box 140, Folder 4)
  - Global Unity Day, June 12, 1983 (Box 140, Folder 5)
  - Ground Breaking Ceremony for Freedom Hall, October 18, 1979 (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - Inauguration of James Deotis Roberts, March 18 - 20, 1980 (Box 140, Folder 7)
  - Installation of the 1978 Honorees in the Gallery of Distinguished Newspaper Publishers, March 17, 1978 (Box 140, Folder 8)
  - Installation of the Rev. Dorothy Freeman Cross, September 18, 1977 (Box 140, Folder 9)
  - Installation Services of the Rev. Odie Millard Hoover, III, October 19, 1980 (Box 140, Folder 10)
  - International Religious Convocation for the Second UN Special Session on Disarmament, 1982 (Box 140, Folder 11)
  - King Week '82: Come Home, January 1982 (Box 140, Folder 12)
  - King Week '83: Charting a Nonviolent Course: Economic Challenges of the Eighties, 1983 (Box 140, Folder 13)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Nonviolent Peace Prize, January 14, 1979 (Box 140, Folder 14)
  - Mississippi Homecoming, June 1981 (Box 140, Folder 15)
  - Morristown Tribute to Dr. Martin Luther King, Sr., October 31, 1976 (Box 140, Folder 16)
  - Nashville Area Junior Chamber of Commerce Award of Merit Banquet, October 25, 1977 (Box 140, Folder 17)
  - New Black Middle Class Prospects, March 27 - 28, 1980 (Box 140, Folder 18)
  - Nonviolence and Human Rights - An Agenda for America, August 1977 (Box 140, Folder 19)
  - Parish Leadership Colloquy, November 22 - 24, 1968 (Box 140, Folder 20)
  - Rededication to the Ideals of Martin Luther King, Jr., February 9, 1978 (Box 140, Folder 21)
  - Relevance of Mordecai Wyatt Johnson for Our Time, January 27, 1978 (Box 140, Folder 22)
  - Religion and Justice, November 4 - 6, 1983 (Box 140, Folder 23)
  - Religious Experiences of Afro-Americans - 1776 - 1976, June 3 - 5, 1976 (Box 140, Folder 24)
  - Responsibility of the Afro-American Church in Politics, October 16 - 17, 1982 (Box 140, Folder 25)
  - Salute to Father Robert C. Chapman, January 19, 1974 (Box 140, Folder 26)
  - Scholar-in-Residence Program of Continuing Education, February - March, 1973 (Box 140, Folder 27)
  - Service of Investiture for Rev. Lawrence Edward Carter, Ph.D., October 7, 1979 (Box 140, Folder 28)
  - Students of the Eighties - New Challenges, New Directions, April 2 - 4, 1981 (Box 140, Folder 29)
  - TA/Gestalt Workshop, June 1977 (Box 140, Folder 30)
  - Testimonial Dinner, April 27, 1980 (Box 140, Folder 31)
  - Union Theological Seminary Summer Conference for Clergy and Laity, 1980 (Box 140, Folder 32)
  - University Choir of Tennessee State University in Concert, March 16, 1980 (Box 140, Folder 33)
  - Welcome Home Alex Haley, May, 1977 (Box 140, Folder 34)
- PERSONAL
  - Appointment Books, Calendars, 1972 - 1981 (Box 140, Folder 35)
  - Appointment Book, 1983 (Box 140, Folder 36)
  - Family (Box 141)
  - Jeff D. Anderson (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - Zee A. Barron (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - Adena Smith (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - Alice Smith (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - Children's Drawings (Box 141, Folder 5)
  - Joy Smith (Box 141, Folder 6)
  - Kelly Miller Smith, Jr. (Box 141, Folder 7)
  - Kelly Miller Smith, Sr. (Box 141, Folder 8)
  - Priscilla Juliette Anderson Smith (Box 141, Folder 9)
  - Smith Family Christmas Card, undated (Box 141, Folder 10)
  - Valerie Lin Smith (Box 141, Folder 11)
  - Wedding Anniversary, 1975 (Box 141, Folder 12)
  - Family and Class Reunion (Box 141, Folder 12)
  - Magnolia Class of 1938 (Box 141, Folder 13)
  - Smith Family, 1974 - 1982 (Box 141, Folder 14)
  - Financial Information (Box 141, Folder 14)
  - Airline Tickets, 1971 - 1982, undated (Box 141, Folder 15)
  - Automobile Expenses, 1955 - 1986 (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - Bank Records, 1956 - 1984 (Box 142, Folder 2)
  - Cash Receipts, 1958 - 1979, undated (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - Credit Union, 1972 - 1975 (Box 142, Folder 4)
  - Hotel Receipts, 1972 - 1983, undated (Box 142, Folder 5)
  - Medical Expenses, 1959 - 1974 (Box 142, Folder 6)
  - Quitclaim Deed, 1980 (Box 142, Folder 7)
  - Telephone Bill, May 28, 1979 (Box 142, Folder 8)
  - University Club, 1971 - 1978 (Box 142, Folder 9)
  - University Club, 1979 - 1980, undated (Box 142, Folder 10)
  - 45 RPM Recording, Scott Parker (Box 142, Folder 11)
  - Hang -in-There Game (Box 142, Folder 12)
  - Homecoming at the Mound Bayou, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 13)
  - Hooker for Governor Fan, undated (Box 142, Folder 14)
  - Minstrel Revue Ticket, 1957 (Box 142, Folder 15)
  - Others' Business Cards (Box 142, Folder 16)
  - Postcards, Stationary (Blank) (Box 142, Folder 17)
  - Power of Attorney, 1970 (Box 142, Folder 18)
  - "Reagan Waiting to Attack Blacks, 1980" (Altered Envelope) (Box 142, Folder 19)
  - Sketch by Ridley, 1979 (Box 142, Folder 20)
  - Subpoenas (Box 142, Folder 21)
- CLIPPINGS
  - Agency Approves Open Way to Fillmore Center Development, undated (Box 142, Folder 22)
  - ARO Workers to Hear Talk by Labor Expert, undated (Box 142, Folder 22)
  - Assuring Freedom to the Free, edited by Arnold M. Rose, 1964 (Box 142, Folder 22)
  - At the Bottom, July 12, 1975 (Box 142, Folder 22)
  - Behavior Modification in the Church Classroom, by William Goodwin and Woodrow W. Jarrel, Jr., 1973 (Box 142, Folder 22)
  - Berber, Moorish and Negro Jews, undated (Box 142, Folder 22)
  - Better Method of Training Black Pastors Advocated, April 18, 1969 (Box 142, Folder 22)
  - The Big Cleanup, 1972 (Box 142, Folder 22)
  - Black Baptists Largest Group, n.d. (Box 142, Folder 22)
  - Black Church in Economic Crisis, February 6, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 22)
  - Black Church is Focal Point for Economic, Social Action, February 6 - 7, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 22)
  - Black Medical College Battles Deficit, 1981 (Box 142, Folder 22)
  - Black Professors on White Campuses, October 2, 1978 (Box 142, Folder 22)
  - Black Studies: Education for Liberation, by William H. McClendon, 1974 (Box 142, Folder 22)
  - Black Theologians Want to Add a Letter by Dr. King to the Bible, August 5, 1979 (Box 142, Folder 22)
  - Books Portray Struggles of Religious Leaders, July 23, 1978 (Box 142, Folder 22)
  - Bush Tells Skeptical Urban League Administration to Offer New Policies, undated (Box 142, Folder 22)
  - "Cabbie" Won't Make It as a Leader of Blacks, undated (Box 142, Folder 22)
  - Cancer as a Metaphor for Death, January 4, 1976 (Box 142, Folder 22)
  - Charities Say They Can't Offset US Aid Cuts, November 14, 1981 (Box 142, Folder 22)
  - Christianity, Islam and Godianism in Nigeria, by O.K. Onyioha, February 9, 1964 (Box 142, Folder 22)
  - Civil Disobedience, undated (Box 142, Folder 22)
  - Cleveland: Fighting Through the Economic Fog, by Jacqueline Moore, undated (Box 142, Folder 23)
  - Conscience and the Vietnam War, undated (Box 142, Folder 23)
  - Court to Decide on Tax Status of Racially Biased Church School, n.d. (Box 142, Folder 23)
  - Death is No Stranger, undated (Box 142, Folder 23)
  - Defending the Indefensible, July 27, 1981 (Box 142, Folder 23)
  - Distortions of 'Roots' on Television Are Inflammatory, undated (Box 142, Folder 23)
  - Eastern Religions: A New Interest and Influence, by Winston L. King, 1970 (Box 142, Folder 23)
  - Education of Black Americans, August 1975 (Box 142, Folder 23)
  - Egyptians of Old Achieved Flight, undated (Box 142, Folder 23)
  - End of Charity Scares New Mother, undated (Box 142, Folder 23)
  - Endangered Voting Rights Defense, undated (Box 142, Folder 23)
  - Escape from Evil, December 14, 1975 (Box 142, Folder 23)
  - Essential Piaget: An Interpretive Reference and Guide, by Howard E. Gruber and J.J. Voneche, 1977 (Box 142, Folder 23)
  - Ethnic Groups Hit Minority Quotas for Universities, August 12, 1977 (Box 142, Folder 23)
  - Extending the Voting Rights Act - An Update, May 1981 (Box 142, Folder 23)
  - Factors Affecting Successful Implementation of Affirmative Action, January 1977 (Box 142, Folder 24)
  - Failure at Geneva, undated Free Nelson Mandela (Box 142, Folder 24)
  - Freedom Rider to Retrace Southern Route, June 8, 1981 (Box 142, Folder 24)
  - From Plessey v. Ferguson to Brown v. Board of Education, August 1975 (Box 142, Folder 24)
  - Fulton Budget Puts Workers, Courts on Top, undated (Box 142, Folder 24)
  - Function of the Negro Church, undated (Box 142, Folder 24)
  - Health, Education and Welfare, August 3, 1977 (Box 142, Folder 24)
  - Helping Hand for Africans, June 24, 1981 (Box 142, Folder 24)
  - Hidden Sources of Negro History, January 18, 1969 (Box 142, Folder 24)
  - Imperialism and Spiritual Freedom: An African View, November 1944 (Box 142, Folder 24)
  - Importance of Considering Man's Spiritual Nature in Treating Those Who Are Sick, January 9, 1963 (Box 142, Folder 24)
  - Indigent Care: Local Hospitals' Role is Debated, May 25, 1981 (Box 142, Folder 24)
  - Internationalization of Torture, undated (Box 142, Folder 24)
  - Interpreter's Bible, Isaiah and The Final Despair and Release, undated (Box 142, Folder 24)
  - It's Time to Put Some Muscle Into Fight Against Apartheid, undated (Box 142, Folder 24)
  - Jew's Right: To Live in Israel, undated (Box 142, Folder 24)
  - Justice Moves Slowly for Some, October 21, 1976 (Box 142, Folder 24)
  - Kahn, Ex-Aide Split on Controls, March 24, 1980 (Box 142, Folder 24)
  - King's Epistle: The Word of God from Birmingham?, November 15, 1979 (Box 142, Folder 24)
  - La Cote Basque, by Truman Capote, undated (Box 142, Folder 24)
  - Lawsuit by Rights Group Seeks Bar to Klansmen Intimidating Blacks, November 5, 1980 (Box 142, Folder 24)
  - Letter to One-Time Friends and Comrades, December 1975 (Box 142, Folder 24)
  - Little has Changed in Racial Relations Since Brown Affair, August 29, 1981 (Box 142, Folder 24)
  - Logan Leader, May 6, 1974 (Box 142, Folder 24)
  - Meharry Looks to the Future, May 4, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 24)
  - Methodists Producing New 'Black Songbook' For All churches, May 19, 1970 (Box 142, Folder 24)
  - Militancy of 'Coloreds' Shocks South Africa's Whites, September 7, 1976 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Muzorewa Agrees to Quit Office, undated (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Negro Baptists Look to Taylor to Head Their Big Denomination, June 16, 1960 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Negro Baptist President Would Quit to Prevent Split, n.d. (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - New Institutionalism, February 1, 1981 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - New Racism, January 1978 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - New South's Like the Old One, January 23, 1977 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Nobel Prize for Diplomatic Clout, October 11, 1977 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Original Communications, 1981 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Ousting the "Pope of Africa,", March 13, 1978 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Patients Say Medical Center Turned Them Away, September 10, 1980 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Pittsburgh Courier, November 5, 1960 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Political 'Murder' - Washington Style, November 18, 1981 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Poorer Black Baptists Go Unheard, September 13, 1981 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Pope Plans Visit to 'Black Madonna,', April 22, 1979 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Private Anger and Public Protest, undated Project on Religion and American Public Life, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Quality of Life, October 8, 1975 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Race Relations, May 14, 1979 - June 7, 1983 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Racism Still Lurks Along Manship Street, undated (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Religion Conventions: Resort's Saving Grace, October 18, 1975 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Religious Organization of the Negro Community, undated (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Reopening the Wilmington 10 Case, November 1, 1976 (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - Rhodesian Fighting Takes Heavy Toll of Innocent, May 28, 1976 (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - Ride to Freedom Rough in, 1961, May 12, 1981 (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - Ryan Kin: How Much Did US Know?, September 27, 1980 Sermon on the Mount, undated (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - Shall the Theological Curriculum Be Modified and How?, 1899 (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - Should Blacks Observe Bicentennial, September 6, 1975 (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - Some Sociological Perspectives of Social Change in the Negro Religious (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - Community and its Leadership, 1957 (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - Some US Blacks Visit South Africa on Business, July 2, 1975 (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - South African Church's Unity Strained, June 29, 1980 (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - State Legislatures React to Campus Riots, Protests, undated (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - State Reports Some Jails Substandard, But Won't Say Which, undated Step in the Right Direction, August 7, 1980 (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - Strength to Love, 1963 (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - Students and the University: The Vacuum, April 8, 1970 (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Study Says Busing Not Education Aid, undated Survival Plan for Sydenham, September 20, 1980 (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - 'Synergy' Aids Body and Soul, September 2, 1978 Teens Burn 4 Georgia Churches (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - This Patient Must Live; There's a Formula for That, May 4, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Three Dimensions of Human Fullness: Poetry, Love and Prayer, by Edward K. Kaplan, 1973 (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Toward an Intern Assessment of Black Theology, 1972 (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Toward a Rationale for Black Studies as an Academic Discipline, by Eugene E. DuBois, undated (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Travels with Brother Will, April 19, 1981 (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Twelve Black Ministers Switch to GOP United States History, undated (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Urgent Need of Reconciliation in Today's World: A Challenge to the Church (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Union Theological Unit Weighs Demand to Raise Panther's Bail, March 15, 1970 (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Uses of Religion in the South by Samuel S. Hill, 1967 (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - White America Becoming Paranoid, November 15, 1975 (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - White Meharry President Causes Local Grad Concern, March 14, 1981 (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - With God All Things Are Possible, 1980 (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Who Listens to the NAACP?, July 8, 1980 (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Woman's Role Is Changing in US, undated (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Women Should Question These Statistics, December 1, 1980 (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Young Clerics More Liberal, Study Shows, December 15, 1969 (Box 143, Folder 3)
- MISCELLANEOUS
  - Advent and Lenten Folders (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - Benjamin E. Mays Institute and Residential Center for Minority Graduate Students, Discussion Draft, August 31, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 5)
  - Bibliographies, Book Lists (Box 143, Folder 6)
  - Brochures (Box 143, Folder 7)
  - Dawson Five (Box 143, Folder 8)
  - Democratic Study Group Special Report: Reagan's War on Black America, September 29, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 9)
  - Dick Gregory Dollar Bill (Box 143, Folder 10)
  - Egyptian, Greek and Israeli currency (Box 143, Folder 11)
  - Elizabeth City State University Handbook of Religious Activities, 1972 - 1973 (Box 143, Folder 12)
  - Four Sermons on Job by Theodore Parker Ferris, March 1959 (Box 143, Folder 13)
  - Government Reports (Box 143, Folder 14)
  - Joint Committee on Economic Development Preliminary Draft of Proposal, undated (Box 143, Folder 14)
  - Minority Business Enterprise; Participation in Contracts and Programs Funded by Department of Transportation, May 17, 1972 (Box 143, Folder 14)
  - Public Law 92-318, Higher Education, June 23, 1972 (Box 143, Folder 14)
  - Harlem Opera Society, undated (Box 143, Folder 15)
  - Hospital Corporation of America (Box 143, Folder 16)
  - Impact of Selected Domestic Program Cuts, March 12, 1981 (Box 143, Folder 17)
  - Israel (Box 143, Folder 18)
  - Legislative Bills of Interest, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 19)
  - Minority Marketing A Continuing Challenge, 1979 (Box 143, Folder 20)
  - Newsletters (Box 143, Folder 21)
  - Our Stake in the Urban Condition, Pertinent Papers (Box 143, Folder 22)
  - Poems (Box 143, Folder 23)
  - Press Releases, 1979 - 1980 (Box 143, Folder 24)